Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Αντιλαμβούς όσων ελεήσων και διαφύλαξον ημάς ο Θεός της η χάρη Της
Κυρία Ελέησον
της Παραγίας Αχράντου υπερευλογημένης εν τόξου δεσποινήσιμον Θεοτόπου και υπαρθένου Μαρίας
με τα πάντα αγία μνημονεύσαντες εαυτούς και αλληλούς και πάσαν την ζωή νημόν Χριστό το Θεό παραθώμεθα
Συ Κύριε
Ότι πρέπει συμπάσα δόξα, τιμή και προσκύνη.
Εις το Πατρί και το Υιό και το Άγιο Πνεύμα, την δίν και αηκέις τους αιώνας των αιώνων.
Αμήν, Θεός Κυρίος και Επεφανένημην, ευλογημένος ο ερχόμενος εν ονόματι Κυρίου.
Εξομολογήστε το Κυρίο και επικαλήστε το όνομα του Άγιον αυτού.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Εν τικετιαν ειρηνή του Κυρίου δε ηθόμεν, αντιλαβούς όσων ελέησον και διαφύλαξον ημάς ο Θεός της ηχάρητης.
Ειρηνή ελέησον.
Της Παναγίας Αχράντου υπερευλογημένης εν τόξου δεσποινήσιμον Θεοτόκου και υπαρεθένου Μαρίας με τα πάντων των Αγίων.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Olami me pati, ala fosson mila, oi, et fosson sotirvus.
From my youth many passions
Suntes ion eschinti te apoi tu,
Suciriu, os hortos garpiri, es est e aperit.
exsiramenim.
Oxa Patris,
Eio
e Agio
legmati,
Agio legmati,
Amen.
Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν, Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν, Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν, Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν, Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν, Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν, Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν, Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν, Κύριε, Άλλα Ισόν.
Ελέη και εκθυρμής και φιλάνθρωπία του μονογενού σου, Ιού μεθ' ου ευλογητός εις,
Εσύ είναι το Παναγίο και αγαθό και ζωπιός του Πνεύματος.
Amen.
The barren one bears the Theotokos, the nourisher of our lives.
The prayer with the sigh, sterile and barren, of Joachim and of Anna,
was well received in the ears of the Lord.
It unbound them, and they blossomed the fruit that brings life to the world.
For while he on the mountain did offer a prayer,
she in the garden the reproach did bear.
But then with joy the barren one bears the Theotokos,
η πηγή της ζωής εκ της θύρας στήκτεται, η χάρη σκαρπογόνη λαμπρός απάρχεται.
Εφραίνου Ιωάκημ, της Θεοτόπου γεννήτωρ γεννόμενος,
που και στην άλλο σωσή των γηγενών γεννητώρων Θεό λείπτε.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Igartheo docos corim, tu Theutos kinoma,
to Panagionoros, via sui min dedorite.
Praise Him with the sound of trumpet, praise Him with the harp and lyre.
What a paradoxical miracle that the fountain of life from a...
and wife is born, that graceful
gent may commence to bear its fruit and
sport. Be joyous, O Joachim,
having become the God-bearer's progenitor.
There is no one else like you
in generations of paternity,
O godly one, for the God-receiving
being made in
Ευλογημένη Βασιλεία του Πατρός και του Υιού και του Αγίου Πνεύματος
νυν και αηκέις τους αιώνας των αιώνων
εν ειρήνη του Κυρίου δεηθώ με
υπέρ της άνωθεν ειρήνης και της σωτηρίας των ψυχών ημών του Κυρίου δεηθώ με
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Υπέρ της ειρηνής του σύμπαντος κόσμου ευταθείας των Αγίων του Θεού Εκκλησιών και της των πάντων ενώσεως του Κυρίου δεηθόμεν.
Κύριε ελέησο.
Υπέρ του Αγίου οικουτούτου και των μεταπίστευσε βλαβείας και φόβου Θεού Ιησιώδων εν αυτό του Κυρίου δεηθόμεν.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Υπέρ του Αρχιεπισκόπου και Πατρός Σιμών Νικολάου, του Τιμίου Πρεσβυτερίου, της Εγκριστώδια Κονίας, παντός του Κλήρου και του Λαού, του Κυρίου δεηθόμε.
Υπέρ του Ευσεύγου Σιμών Έθνους, πάσης αρχής και εξουσίας εν αυτόν, του Κυρίου δεηθόμε.
εαυτούς και αλληλούς και πάσαν την ζωή νοιμών Χριστώ το Θεό παραθώμεθα
ότι σώτο κράτος και σου εστίν η βασιλεία και οι δύναμεις
και η δόξα του Πατρός και του Υιού και του Αγίου Πνεύματος
νυν και αηκέης τους αιώνας των αιώνων
Αμήν.
I shall set upon your throne one from the fruit of your loins.
Save us, O Son of God, who are wondrous in the saints.
We sing to you, Alleluia.
The Lord has chosen Zion.
He has chosen her for his dwelling.
Save us, O Son of God, who are wondrous in the saints.
We sing to you, Alleluia.
For you are a good and loving God,
and to you we give up glory,
and to the Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit,
now and forever and to the ages of ages.
Amen.
Ευχαριστώ, Ιησού, για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την ευκαιρία του Θεού και για την
Alleluia.
As they cry out to you
The bearing one bears the Theotokos
The nourisher of our lives
To the Lord we give thanks
The Holy One, the Lord our God
And you, we praise you
We are in contact
και το Υιό και το Άγιο Πνεύμα την δίνει και αεί
και εις τους αιώνας των αιώνων.
Αμήν, Άγιος ο Θεός,
Άγιος η Σύνος,
Άγιος ο Θεός,
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Let us be attentive.
My soul magnifies the Lord and my spirit rejoices in God my Savior.
For he has regarded the humility of his servants.
Wisdom.
The reading is for...
From St. Paul's letter to the Philippians.
Let us be attentive.
Brethren, have this mind among yourselves,
which is yours in Jesus Christ,
who though he was in the form of God,
did not count equality with God a thing to be grasped,
but emptied himself, taking the form of a servant,
being born in the likeness of men,
and being found in human form he humbled himself to the cross.
himself and became obedient unto death even death on a cross therefore God has
highly exalted him and bestowed on him the name which is above every name that
at the name of Jesus every knee every knee should bow in heaven and on earth
and under the earth and every tongue confess that Jesus Christ is Lord to the
The glory of God the Father.
Ὁ πώς υπό το κράτους οὐ πάντοτε φιλαθόμενης ἡ δόξαν ἀναπέμπωμεν,
τὸ Πατρί καὶ τὸ Υιόν καὶ τὸ ἄγιον Πνεύμα τὴν ἴν καὶ ἀηκαίης τοὺς αἰώνας τὸν αἰώνων.
Ὁ δὲ σάξος τὸς ἐθωμένους τὴς ἐπὸ τοῦς ἀγώτουσις ἀμὸς πρόσχης τὸς ἐστιν ἀγωμένους,
Μαζιλεύει τις δόντσες του Καρύδια Κνήση με ένα κέφαλο χρόνο και αυτές θα σκοτεινούσαν την άμυση.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
with all the saints
that has commended ourselves
and one another
and our whole life
to Christ our God.
Through the night
of your only begotten Son
with your blessed
Holy Spirit
through the Holy
and the Holy
and your living
Spirit
νυν και αηκέης τους αιώνας των αιώνων.
Ειρήνη πάση
με το πνεύμα εντύσσου.
Αγαπήσομαι να λύλωση, να ενωμονία ομολογήσομαι.
Αγαπήστε τον Κύριο Ιησού Χριστέ, με τα ευγεία μου.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
broke and gave it to his holy disciples
and apostles saying
Amen.
Likewise after supper he took the cup saying
Drink of it all of you
This is my blood of the new covenant
Shed for you and for many
For the forgiveness of sin
Remembering therefore the saving command of the Savior
for all that came to pass for the sake of the cross.
the tomb, the resurrection, the third day, the ascension to heaven.
In throng and at the right hand of the Father, the second glorious coming.
Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done, on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread, and forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those who sin.
trespass against us, and lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil. For thine is the kingdom, the power,
and the glory of the Father, and the Son, and the Holy Spirit,
now and forever and to the ages of
ages. Amen.
Peace be with all.
And with your spirit.
Let us bow our heads.
to the Lord.
Those who sail, travel with those who travel
and heal the sick physician of our souls and bodies.
By the grace, mercy, and love for us of your only begotten Son,
with whom you are blessed,
together with your all-holy, good, and life-giving Spirit,
now and forever and to the ages of ages.
Amen.
your inheritance.
We have seen the true
life. We have received
the heavenly spirit.
We have the true faith.
Worshiping the undivided
Trinity.
For the Trinity
has been
found.
for all you do
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
We thank you, Lord, for your mercy.
incarnation, and then to his crucifixion, to his resurrection, and to his ascension.
Those events really start in some way today with the birth of the Theotokos. She is born.
For Christ to be born, the Theotokos must be born. So this is the beginning of that series
of events that leads to ultimately the salvation of the whole world.
happens today. So let's never forget
September 8th is not
just a random day in the
year. It's the beginning of
the chronicle, in some ways,
of salvation. So God bless you.
Thank you for being here today.
And Church, please come forward for
Andithoro.